http://www.centralbank.org.bb/privacy-policy

Licensed Financial Institutions
Confidential Statement Forms (Updated)
Foreign Investment Form
Foreign Currency Form (Not For Imports)
Foreign Currency Form (For Imports)
Periodic Payments Form (Original and Duplicates)
TR Form (Original and Duplicates)
Foreign Account Tax Compliance Act (FATCA)
ForeignExchangeFee
Banknotes
Banknotes
New Family of Banknotes/ The 2013 Series
Previous Series (2007, 1999)
strongly committed to maintaining
the privacy of your personal information.
identifiable as such, like
your name, address, e-mail address, or phone number,
and that is not
otherwise publicly available.
The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices
Detection Monitoring Notification
of Changes to Policy If users have questions or concerns regarding this
statement, they should contact the Central Bank of Barbados at: Central
Bank Of Barbados
Tom Adams Financial Centre,
Spry Street,
Bridgetown
Barbados,
West Indies Postal
P. O. Box 1016,
Bridgetown,
Barbados,
West Indies BB11126 E-mail:
info@centralbank.org.bb
Tel:
(246) 436-6870
Personal Information
Collected This information is only collected by the Central Bank of Barbados if
you
supply it to us. Supply can take two forms, namely by you sending
automatically gather any specific personal information
from you.
Any information sent to the Central Bank of Barbados
is maintained by
the Central Bank of Barbados for the following reasons: For the purpose of processing your request or inquiry; For use by the Central Bank of Barbados
in furthering its mission
of promoting and maintaining stability, safety,
integrity and public
confidence in the capital market of Trinidad and Tobago To be shared by the Central Bank of Barbados with third parties,
including other government agencies, in order to advance the purpose for
which
you provide the information; and To disclose, if required by law, for example, to respond to a
police investigation, subpoena or court order.
Please note, if you decide to send e-mail to the Central Bank of
Barbados you are consenting to the Central Bank
of Barbados
using the
information provided therein, including personal identifying
information,
in accordance with this notice, unless you expressly state
in the e-mail your
objection to any use(s).Information
Collected About Your Visit to the website The Central Bank of Barbados automatically collects and
stores the following information about you when you visit our website: The date and time the request was received. Your Internet Protocol (IP) address or the proxy address of your
Internet Service Provider (e.g. AOL, CompuServe, and so on). The name and IP address of the Central Bank of Barbados web
server that received and logged the request. The resource on a Central Bank of Barbados web server accessed as a
result of the request, such as the web page, image, and so on. The query in the request. This field captures any criteria or
parameters issued with a query, such as the name of a reporting issuer
or
market actor. The name and version of your Web browser (e.g. Internet Explorer
6.0 or Netscape 7.0). The content of any sent or received cookie. The Uniform Resource Locator (URL) that was accessed before the
user made a request for Central Bank of Barbados's web server. The URL
may
be an outside address that is not related to the Central Bank of
Barbados
server. Other status codes and values resulting from the Web server
responding to the request received: HTTP status code, Windows NT code,
number
of bytes sent, number of bytes received, duration (in seconds)
to fulfill the
request, server port number addressed, and protocol
version. Information on the screen resolution setting of your PC (e.g.
800
x 600, 1280 x 1024, etc.). This information will be used to adjust
Central
Bank of Barbados
design standards so the pages we produce will
be as readable as possible on
your computer display. Use of CookiesA cookie is a piece of a file stored on the user’s computer
tied to
information about the user. At present this site does not use any
cookies. Intrusion Detection
Monitoring This computer system employs software security programs to
monitor
network traffic to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change
information, or otherwise cause damage. Such attempts are strictly
prohibited.
Except for authorized law enforcement investigations, no
other attempts are
made to identify individual users or their usage
habits.Notification of
Changes to Policy If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post
those
changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we
deem
appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we
was collected.
Confidential Statement Forms (Updated)
Foreign Currency Form (Not For Imports)
Foreign Currency Form (For Imports)
Periodic Payments Form (Original and Duplicates)
TR Form (Original and Duplicates)
Foreign Account Tax Compliance Act (FATCA)
ForeignExchangeFee
Banknotes
Banknotes
New Family of Banknotes/ The 2013 Series
Previous Series (2007, 1999)
Collected About Your Visit to the websiteUse of CookiesIntrusion Detection
Tom Adams Financial Centre,
Spry Street,
Bridgetown
Barbados,
West Indies
E-mail:
